

#### **Contact**

**Phone** +90 544 412 40 80

**Email** enesmalikdmn@gmail.com

Address
Erzene Mah. 51.sok. Bornova / İzmir

#### **Education**

2016-2023 **Ege University** 

2010-2015 Kuleli Military High School

### **Skills**

- Tailwind, Bootstrap Material UI
- Devextreme, Vuetify, PrimeVue
- UI/UX
- HTML/CSS
- · Vuex, Pinia, Redux Toolkit
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Vue.js (v2 v3)
- React, NextJS
- Jest, Cypress
- CanvasJS
- ThreeJs
- GraphQL

# Language

English (Upper Intermediate)
German (Beginner)

# **Enes Malik** Duman

## Frontend Developer

# **Summary**

I graduated from Ege University, Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering. Disciplined temperament, eager to learn new skills, prone to leadership capacity, became a leader at Kuleli Military High School. I am currently a software engineer passionate about learning new technologies. I have improved myself in subjects such as leadership and teamwork. I have been working as a Frontend Developer since 2021. I have been working as a Frontend team leader for three months.

# **Experience**

**Q** 2021 - Present

Digitastic | Izmir, Turkey

#### **Frontend Developer**

Mid-level frontend developer in a company that works on digital accounting. I have carried out projects using technologies such as Vue.js, React, Typescript, Pinia, Redux Toolkit, Canvas.js, Vue-query both alone and with a team. I worked closely with designers to ensure proper implementation of UI components and visuals. I adhered to Agile methodologies including Scrum and Kanban.

2021 - 2021

Digitastic | Izmir, Turkey

#### **Frontend Developer Intern**

I took training on HTML and CSS and learned how to use responsive design and different CSS frameworks. I used what I learned by developing projects using Javascript, VueJs and NodeJs.

#### Certification

O 2024 - Present

**Data Structure (Computer Concepts, Online)** 

Data structures lesson using Javascript programming language.

2024 - 2024

React - 401 (Turkcell, Online)

A training consisting of four stages, React 101, 201, 301 and 401, covering topics such as fetching (axios), routing, form management, localization, deployment process, services, tests and creating and publishing a React library.

2021 - 2021

**CS50: Introduction to Computer Science (Harvard University, Online)** 

An introduction to the intellectual enterprises of computer science and the art of programming.

## Reference

Adem Akdoğan, PhD

Software Developer, Digitastic

**Phone:** +90 (554) 441 03 19 **Email:** a.akdogan@digitastic.app